어지러운 전국 시대.
It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over
Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
Karakuri Martial Artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri Martial Artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi is here-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
in the center of the world to become
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! the strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight the utmost with the stillness
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
His eyes shined! Musashi!
애도가 부러져 침울해진 코지로를 위해 무사시는 아마쿠사 섬에 향하지만 이카즈치에게 잡히고 만다.
For Kojirō, whose beloved sword was broken, Musashi heads to Amakusa Island, but he gets caught by Ikazuchi.
그렇지만 코지로는 전설의 비검, 봉황환을 손에 넣어 그 대단한 힘으로 이카즈치를 쓰러트렸다.
But Kojirō obtained the legendary secret sword, Hououmaru, and used its great power to take down Ikazuchi.
어라?!
무사시는 죽소
What?!
Musashi Dies
뭐라? 아마쿠사 섬의 우리 무기 공장이?
What? You mean, our weapon factory in Amakusa Island?
예. 무사시, 코지로, 센히메 일행이 사이고를 데리고 와서 했습니다.
Yes. Musashi, Kojirō, and Senhime's group came and done it.
무사시인가...
Musashi, eh...
그러니까 충고했습니다. 놈들은 어서 처리하는 게 좋다고.
That's why I advised you to take care of them as soon as possible.
흥, 단순하게 아이일 뿐이라 생각했더니.
Hmph. I thought he was a simple child.
놈들이 시치미를 떼고 있으니 이렇게.
This happens because they're making poker faces.
뭐, 안심하세요. 그런 패거리에게 끌려다닐 시라누이 일족이 아닙니다.
Well, don't worry about that. We, Shiranui Clan do not get taken over by those small bunch.
센짱, 같이 가오!
Sen-chan, wait for me-dasu!
흥! 정말 진짜!
Hmph! Really!
왜 화내오...
Why are you angry at me-dasu?
맨날맨날 네 멋대로 행동만 해서 엄청 위험에 처했던 건 알고 있어?
Do you even know that we were in dire crisis just because you were acting on your own?!
원래라면 목숨이 몇개고 있어도 부족했어!
Our lives should already have been exhausted by now!
미안하오...
I'm sorry-dasu...
보통이라면 죽었을 거야!
We might have been died!
그렇소...
Yeah...
자기 생각만 하고, 남 걱정은 안 하냐?
You only think about yourself, but never worries about everyone else!
그러니까, 계속 사과하오!
That's why I'm keeping to apologize-dasu!
흥! 정말 반성하고 있냐?
Hmph! Are you actually reflecting?
하고 있소.
I am-dasu.
그럼 태도로 증명해 봐.
Then show me by actions.
태도이오?
By actions-dasu?
반성 태도 제 1.
The first action of reflection.
제 2.
The second.
미안
SORRY
제 3.
The third.
제 4.
The fourth.
제 5.
The fifth.
제 6.
The sixth.
제 7.
The seventh.
무사시!
Musashi!
멈춰, 무사시!
Stop right there, Musashi!
참수다! 너 따위 용서 못 해!
You're getting decapitated! I can't forgive you!
-무사시!
-봐 주시오!
-Musashi!
-Please forgive me-dasu!
이렇게 해 주마!
You'll suffer this!
저건 쥬베 님.
That's Mr. Jube!
쥬베가?
Jube?
시라누이 일족에 대해 뭔가 알았어?
Did you find something about Shiranui Clan?
예.
Yessir.
보아하니 시라누이 일족은 이 운젠 산의 어딘가에 본거지를 두고 있는 것 같습니다.
It seems that Shiranui Clan has their base somewhere in Unzen Mountain.
운젠 산?
Mt. Unzen?
센히메 님도 충분히 조심해 주십시오.
Please be careful, Senhime.
예.
Got it.
운젠 산이오...
Mt. Unzen, is it-dasu...
무사시! 어디 가?
Musashi! Where are you going?
오줌이오.
To pee-dasu.
알고 있지?
Do you remember?
그렇소! 행동은 자중하오!
Yes, of course! I have to restrain myself-dasu!
그렇게까지 할 필요는 없소만...
You don't have to do that-dasu...
안 돼! 어디에 갈 지 몰라!
No way! You might go somewhere!
센히메 님.
Senhime.
시간이 너무 걸리잖아.
He's taking too much time.
무사시! 언제까지 쉬하고 있을 거야!
Musashi! How long does it take for you to pee?!
멧돼지다!
A boar!
센히메 님! 같이 가요!
Senhime! Wait for me!
코지로! 어떻게 좀 해 봐!
Kojirō! Do something!
맡겨 주세요, 센히메 님!
Leave it to me, Senhime!
간류 미스터 코지로가 상대하겠다!
Ganryu Mister Kojirō will face you!
그래, 덤벼 봐라!
Yeah, face me!
비검! 츠바메가에시!
Secret sword, Tsubamegaeshi!
코지로! 불쌍하니까 죽이면 안 돼!
Kojirō! Don't kill them, as they're poor!
어?
What?!
시라누이 일족의 본거지만 알면 내 것이오!
As soon as I find out where Shiranui Clan's base is, they're mine-dasu!
이번에야말로 먼저 공격을 걸어서 오명을 만회하겠소!
I'll attack first this time, and clear my bad reputatoin-dasu!
센짱도 날 다시 볼 것이오!
Sen-chan will reevaluate me, too-dasu!
진짜! 정말 무사시 놈!
That damn Musashi!
놈은 용서할 수 없습니다! 할복하게 만듭시다!
He's unforgivable! Let's make him disembowel himself!
할복이야, 할복이야! 참수야, 사형이야, 할복!
Disembowel! Disembowel! Decapitate! Execute! Disembowel!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
이, 이건 할머니 유품인 방울이야. 할머니가 말했어. 이 방울이 둘로 갈라지면 불길한 일이 일어날 거라고.
T- this is my grandmother's bells. She told me that when these bells split into two, something bad will happen.
이만큼 쌓인 걸 보니 엄청 나쁜 예감이 들어...
Seeing all those ill omens at once, I have a terrible foreboding...
내게 그런 건 안 먹힌다!
That does not work against me!
그건 좀 먹히는군!
That worked, though!
괜찮나, 벤케이!
Are you alright, Benkei?!
우시와카 님! 죄송합니다! 제가 정신을 좀 놨습니다!
Ushiwaka! I'm sorry! I let myself go easy!
전투는 진검 승부. 한순간의 틈이 생명을 좌우합니다.
A battle is a real fight with real swords. One opening can be fatal.
알겠습니다!
Understood!
보아하니 이대로는 우리가 불리합니다. 한번에 끝장냅시다!
It seems that it's won't work favorably to us at this rate. Let's finish this at once!
예!
Yessir!
텐구류 부채춤!
Tengu Style Fan Dance!
어차피 나와 우시와카 님에게는 못 당해낼 테다!
You aren't defeating me and Ushiwaka!
건방진 놈들.
Impudent bastards!
너는!
You!
용암의 겐바
Genba of Lava
운젠 산이라고 하면 더 말할 것도 없이 다 아는 겐바 님이시다.
Everyone recognizes me, Genba, just by Mt. Unzen!
시라누이 일족을 막아서면 어떻게 되는지 알려주마!
I'll show you what it means to stand in the way of Shiranui Clan!
우시와카 님! 여긴 제게 맡기쇼!
Ushiwaka! Leave this to me!
후후, 벤케이. 맡깁니다.
Benkei. I will do so.
시라누이 요술 용암탄!
Shiranui magic, Lava Shell!
벤케이!
Benkei!
이 세상에 악이 있는 한 퇴치하는 것이 나의 사명!
As long as evil exists in this world, my mission is to exterminate them!
이천일류의 검의 차이를 보여 주겠소!
I'll show you the difference of the swords of Nitenichiryu-dasu!
우시와카 씨! 벤케이 씨! 오랜만이오! 일만 냥 무예 대회에서의 은혜를 갚아 드리겠소!
Mr. Ushiwaka! Mr. Benkei! It's been a while-dasu!
I'll pay back the favor you did to me in Ten Thousand Ryo Martial Arts Competition-dasu!
그건 고맙습니다. 맡기겠습니다.
Thank you. We're entrusting it on you.
무사시! 그 놈이 던지는 거 조심해라!
Musashi! Be careful of what he throws!
알겠소!
Understood-dasu!
일격에 둘로 철모 나누기!
Divide steel helmet into two with one strike!
무사시!
Musashi!
무사시.
Musashi.
(무시: 벌레)
(Mushi: Bug)
날아서 불에 뛰어드는 여름의 무사시인가.
Musashi has flown into the flame.
아파, 아파! 엄마!
It hurts! Mommy!
-엄마!
-왜 그러니, 무사시?
-Mommy!
-What's wrong, Musashi?
나, 넘어졌어.
I fell down.
저런, 아팠겠다. 엄마 손은 약손이지?
That must've hurt! Pain, pain, go away!
자! 이제 괜찮지?
Look! You're fine now!
응, 이제 안 아퍼.
Yeah, I'm good now!
엄마...
Mommy...
엄마!
Mommy!
꿈이오...
It was a dream...
무사시 씨? 일어나셨나요?
Mr. Musashi? Did you wake up?
엄마...
Mommy...
안 돼요, 무사시 씨.
No, Mr. Musashi!
히미코의 속셈은 무엇인가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
What could be Himiko up to? Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
실례합니다. 묻고 싶은게 있습니다만, 몹시 게걸스럽고 얼빠진 얼굴을 한 카라쿠리 무예가를 보셨습니까?
Excuse me. I'd like to ask you if you see a Karakuri martial artist who's very gluttonous and half-witted?
아니.
No.
머리 크고, 다리 짧고, 나 배고프오! 이라던가 멍청하게 말하는 이상한 사람 못 봤어요?
Did you see a weirdo with a big head and short legs who shouts I'm hungry-dasu! around?
몰라요.
I don't know.
이 주변에 있는 단고집이나 사츠마아게집에는 죄다 물어봤습니다만 무사시를 봤다는 사람은 아무도 없습니다.
I've asked all Dango or Satsumaage house around here, but it seems that nobody saw him.
그거야!
That's it!
뭔가 좋은 아이디어가?
Doyou have a good idea?
초상화를 그려서 찾아 보자!
Let's try finding by drawing a portrait!
초, 초상화!?
P- portrait?!
됐어?
Did you do it?
아니, 아, 아직입니다.
No, I- I'm not ready yet.
괜찮잖아, 보여줘!
It's alright! Show me!
어, 그게, 좀...
Well, that's, kinda...
뭐야, 이거.
What's this?
음, 저, 어릴 적부터 그림 잘 못 그렸으니...
Err, drawing was not my best when I was young...
이제 센히메 님께 기대하는 수밖에 없습니다!
Now our only hope is you, Senhime!
아, 싫어, 나도 좀...
Uh, no, I'm not ready too.
나, 어린이일 때부터 소녀 만화만 읽어서 이런 그림밖에 못 그려.
I only read girl comics since I was a child, and thus this is the only kind of drawing I can draw.
이런 기분 나쁜 기억을 하는 것도 전부 무사시 탓입니다!
The reason we're being reminded of bad memories is also Musashi's fault!
찾아내면 참수시킬 거야!
He'll be decapitated when we get him!
벤케이 님에 우시와카 님!
Mr. Benkei and Mr. Ushiwaka!
어? 무사시가?
What? Musashi did?!
예. 꽤 상처를 입어서.
Yes. With serious injuries.
우리가 절벽 아래로 내려갔을 때는 모습도 그림자도 없었쇼.
When we went down the cliff, we couldn't see his form or shadow.
그렇게 상처를 입었다면 멀리 갔을 리가 없다.
If he's really that injured, he shouldn't be far away.
무슨 일이 있던 것인지... 우리가 곁에 있으면서...
How do we not know when we were with him...
운젠 산에서 일어난 일이라는 거지.
It all happened in Mt. Unzen.
-코지로!
-네. 즉시.
-Kojirō!
-Got it. Right away.
나쁜 예감이 맞지 않으면 좋겠는데...
I hope my bad foreboding is wrong...
맛있소.
It's tasty!
정말 나 히미코 씨가 구해줘서 살았소!
Really, you saved me-dasu, Ms. Himiko!
-자.
-아.
-Open.
-Ahh.
밥도 히미코 씨가 상냥해서인지 더 맛있소.
It tastes even great, maybe because you're so kind-dasu, Ms. Himiko!
어라, 벌써 텅 비었네요. 무사시 씨, 더 먹을래요?
Hey, it's empty already. Mr. Musashi, do you want to have more?
그렇소! 더 먹소!
Yes-dasu! I'll eat more-dasu!
잠깐만 기다려 주세요.
Please wait for a moment.
준비해 두라고 겐바에게 전해라.
Tell Genba to be prepared.
히미코 씨!
Ms. Himiko!
아, 예!
Y- yeah!
실례하오. 화장실 어디이오?
Excuse me-dasu. Where's the toilet-dasu?
네, 네, 제가 데려가 드릴게요.
Yes, I'll take you to there.
정말, 이러고 있으니 나 엄마하고 있는 것 같소!
Being like this feels like I'm with my mother-dasu!
제가 그렇게 무사시 씨의 어머님과 닮았나요?
Am I really that like your mother, Mr. Musashi?
아니, 나, 엄마하고 본 적 없소.
Well, I have never met my mother-dasu.
음?
Hm?
정신이 드니, 혼자였소...
When I woke up, I was alone-dasu...
그렇군요.
I see.
만약 있다면, 분명 히미코 씨 같지 않을까 하오.
If she exists, then I guess that she's just like you, Ms. Himiko!
좋은 기분이오. 운젠까지 온 보람이 있었소!
I feel great-dasu. It really worth it to come to Unzen-dasu!
그렇소! 이 운젠은 시라누이 일족의 본거지가 있소!
Right-dasu! Shiranui's base is at here, Unzen-dasu!
어? 시라누이 일족? 음, 그건 무섭네요.
What? Shiranui Clan? Well, that's scary!
히미코 씨, 이런 곳에 있으면 안 되오. 더 안전한 곳에!
Ms. Himiko, you shouldn't be at a place like this-dasu. Go to somewhere safer-dasu!
(지고쿠다니: 지옥곡)
(Jigokudani: lit. Hell Valley)
예, 여기에 온 건 지고쿠다니라고 하는 용암이 분출하는 명소가 있어, 거기에 기도하면 소원이 이루어진대서...
Erm, I came here because I heard that there is a famous place called Jigokudani where lava sprouts,
and one's wish will be realized by praying.
함께 뵈러 가요! 그리고 둘이서 운젠에서 내려가면 되겠지요?
Let's go see that place together! And then we'll get off Mt. Unzen.
그건 좋은 생각이오!
That's a good idea-dasu!
네, 케로키치, 수고했어! 전 개구리를 먹여온 지 80년째입니다! 이젠 대화도 가능해요!
Good job, Kerokichi! It's been 80 years since I fed this frog!
오늘의 손님들은 좋은 손님들이었다고 하네요!
He says that today's audiences were excellent!
그럼 이 제가 79년의 연구 끝에 만들어 낸 것이, 이 두꺼비 기름!
Now, let me introduce the result of my 79 years of research: Toad Oil!
그래요, 이게 그 근방에 있는 다른 두꺼비 기름과는 다릅니다.
Yes, this Toad Oil is completely different from your everyday toad oils!
사마귀 가득한 두꺼비에게서 골라낸 것입니다.
It is specially taken from toads full of warts!
자, 모이신 여러분! 사마귀 주변에 사방으로 거울을 둡니다! 그럼 두꺼비는 자신의 모습의 추함에 주르륵 주르륵 하고 기름을 흘립니다.
Look! First, put mirror in every direction around that toad with warts!
By doing that, the toad will sweat oils, suffering its own unsightliness!
그걸 모으면 이렇게 두꺼비 기름이 짜자잔! 하고 나옵니다!
And by collecing that, we can get Toad Oil like this!
대단해!
Awesome!
아, 거기, 할머니. 거울 보면 할머니도 기름땀 흘릴 것 같으시군요.
Hey, there, granny! You look like you'd sweat oil too if you see mirrors!
뭐?!
What?!
자, 그럼, 다시, 여러분! 어?
Well then, again, Everyone! Huh?
무, 무사시다!
I- it's Musashi!
저 여성은 누구지? 무사시가 데리고 다니기에는 너무 예뻐.
Who is that woman? She is too pretty for Musashi to take.
게다가 저긴 지고쿠다니 방향.
Moreover, that way is to Jigokudani.
-어이!
-뭐 하고 있어!
-Hey!
-What are you doing?!
아, 네, 네, 네! 자, 그럼 이 두꺼비 기름, 평소라면 100문이지만, 오늘은 더 깎아서 50문입니다!
Oh, right, right, right! This Toad Oil is usually 100 mons, but for today only, it's 50 mons!
지고쿠다니
Jigokudani
대단하오. 이런 건 처음 보오!
It's amazing-dasu! I never saw something like this-dasu!
무사시 씨, 무서워요?
Mr. Musashi, are you scared?
아니, 카라쿠리 무예가가 이런 걸로! 단지 무사다운 거동이오!
No, it's nothing more than a prowess of a Karakuri martial artist-dasu!
자, 기도해요.
Then let's pray.
그렇소.
Right-dasu.
내가 제너럴 이에야스를 무너트리고 시라누이 일족의 천하가 올 수 있도록.
To take down General Ieyasu, and for Shiranui Clan to take over the whole country.
지팡구 제일의 무예가가 될 수 있도록, 그리고, 시라누이 일족을 퇴치할 수 있도록.
To become the number one martial artist of Jipangu, and to take care of Shiranui Clan.
그걸 넘어서, 언제라도 배 가득 먹을 수 있도록. 만두라던가, 팥과자라던가, 또...
Even further, to eat enough whenever I want so that I can feel full, like dumplings, dorayaki, and...
떨어져라!
Fall!
흥, 잘 피했군. 그러나 이번엔 끝장이다!
Hmph, that was a nice evasion. But you're really going down this time!
저놈은 그때 그놈! 이번엔 방심 안 하오!
You're that guy from before! I'm not letting my guard down this time-dasu!
히미코 씨에게는 무예가의 고집을 걸고 손가락 하나 못 대게 하갰소!
I won't let you even lay your finger on Ms. Himiko, risking the pride of a martial artist-dasu!
그러냐. 재밌네.
Oh, is that so? How interesting.
히미코 씨, 지금 달아나시오! 내가 막아 보이겠소!
Ms. Himiko, run away right now-dasu! I'll stop him no matter what-dasu!
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
가엾지만 상관 없다. 잘 끝내라, 겐바.
He has my pity, but it won't stop this. Finish him, Genba.
끝이구나, 무사시!
It's end for you, Musashi!
시라누이 요술 용암탄!
Shiranui Magic, Lava Shell!
-쥬베 씨!
-무사시 님. 여긴 제게 맡겨 주세요.
-Mr. Jube!
-Mr. Musashi. Leave this to me.
-자, 와라!
-흥, 상대가 누구라도 난 상관 없다!
-You may come!
-Hmph! No matter the enemy, I don't care!
무사시!
Musashi!
-어디 있어!
-무사시!
-Where are you?!
-Musashi!
어, 저기, 거기 행인님.
Excuse me.
네, 뭔 일이라도?
What is it?
무사시라는 자를 찾고 있습니다만 알고 계십니까?
We're looking for someone called Musashi; do you know him?
자, 무사시라... 어디서 들은 거 같은 이름이다만...
Well, Musashi... I think I heard that name before.
-많이 먹고,
-품위 없고,
-He eats a lot.
-He's so vulgar.
-나, 무사시이오! 하고 말하는
-다리 짧은 무예가이오.
-He says I am Musashi-dasu!
-He's a short-legged martial artist.
아, 기억났습니다. 그 분이라면 지고쿠다니 쪽으로 갔어요.
Oh, I remembered him. He went towards Jigokudani.
지고쿠다니에? 고마워요!
To Jigokudani? Thanks!
혹시 그쪽은 지라이얀이?
Could you possibly be Jiraiyan?
아, 아니, 그럴 리 없습니다!
N- no, that's not true!
아, 그렇습니까. 그럼 실례합니다.
Oh, is that so? Then excuse me.
저 놈들, 정말 귀찮게 하는 놈들이야.
Those guys are really annoying.
야규신카게류 순풍의 대도!
Yagyu Shinkage Style, Tailwind Long Sword!
창이 없으면 끝장이겠다!
Without your spear, you're over!
아직 이게 있다!
I still have this!
쥬베 씨, 조심하시오!
Mr. Jube, watch out!
쥬베 씨!
Mr. Jube!
끝장이다!
Time to finish this!
멈춰라!
Stop!
시라누이! 여긴 우리가 상대해 주겠다!
Shiranui! We'll face you from now on!
무사시! 걱정했어!
Musashi! I was worried about you!
미안하오. 이번엔 틀렸다고 생각했소.
I'm sorry-dasu. I thought it was over this time-dasu.
먹어라!
Take this!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
센짱, 위험하오!
Sen-chan, watch out!
무사시!
Musashi!
정의의 히로는 어떤 일이 있어도 안 죽소!
A hero of justice never dies no matter what-dasu!
아미타불이다.
That's death for you.
무사시!
Musashi!
미야모토 마을의 무사시는 죽었다. 너무나도 어이없는 최후였다. 카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드의 주인공은 죽고 말았다.
Musashi from Miyamoto village has died. His final moment was too short.
The main character of Karakuri Kengouden Musashi Road has died.
대체 이 이야기는 어디로 흘러가는가? 기상천외한 다음 이야기를 기다리자!
Where is this story going to? Let's wait for the most fantastic next story!
허공의 주머니에 달이
Sometimes the moon jumps over
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
the pocket of empty sky
큰 소리로 웃으면
Laugh loudly and
내일에는 아침이 와
morning will come tomorrow
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Don't worry too much about losing
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
Keep going! Go for it!
맨손은 강해
A bare hand is strong
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
That's how life is! Look, a chance
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
follows us wagging its tail!
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
찾아온 대영계. 아, 역시 난 죽고 말았소.
The spiritual world has finally called me-dasu. I died and that couldn't be helped-dasu!
그래도, 그리웠던 이시마츠 씨하고 만났으니 뭐, 됐소!
Still, I met Mr. Ishimatsu in a while! Good enough!
슈텐하고 오니히메가 멋대로 설치는 영계에서 나는 대활약하오.
In the spiritual world where Shuten and Onihime are being self-indulgent, I make great activities!
그러나 살아 돌아가기 위해선 어서 삼도내로 돌아가야!
But I have to go back to Sanzu River in order to revive!
다음 이야기! 역시 불사신 무사시이오
Next story! Of Course! Musashi is Immortal
질풍노도의 대영계이오!
It's a stormy great spiritual world-dasu!
다음 이야기
역시 불사신
무사시이오
재미있게 보세요!
Next Story
Of Course!
Musashi is Immortal
We hope you enjoy!